marriagebuilders.com 2001-03-30

# Marriage Builders' Privacy Policy

|    
---|---  
  
### Privacy Policy

Marriage Builders, Inc. does not and will not use information about where you go on our web site, nor give that data out to third parties. We may collect traffic patterns in order to improve the quality of our web site, but we do not review information at the personal level, only the aggregate. 

Please note that the only information automatically logged by [Marriage Builders](http://www.marriagebuilders.com/) is a user's IP address. _IP information in no way identifies the user, simply the Internet Service Provider._

Marriage Builders works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>. 

For information regarding the privacy policy for the Marriage Builders Newsletter, please click on the link below. 

Newsletter Privacy Policy

We hope you will find our information and resources useful. 

Thank you for visiting.   

[HOME](http://www.marriagebuilders.com/) | CONCEPTS | RADIO | Q & A | BOOKS | COUNSEL For comments or suggestions about this web site, please notify the [Web Manager](mailto:webmaster@marriagebuilders.com).  
© 1996-2000 Marriage Builders, Inc. Marriage Builders is a registered trademark of Marriage Builders, Inc.
|    
---|---  
  
### Privacy Policy

Marriage Builders, Inc. does not and will not use information about where you go on our web site, nor give that data out to third parties. We may collect traffic patterns in order to improve the quality of our web site, but we do not review information at the personal level, only the aggregate. 

Please note that the only information automatically logged by [Marriage Builders](http://www.marriagebuilders.com/) is a user's IP address. _IP information in no way identifies the user, simply the Internet Service Provider._

Marriage Builders works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>. 

For information regarding the privacy policy for the Marriage Builders Newsletter, please click on the link below. 

Newsletter Privacy Policy

We hope you will find our information and resources useful. 

Thank you for visiting.   

[HOME](http://www.marriagebuilders.com/) | CONCEPTS | RADIO | Q & A | BOOKS | COUNSEL For comments or suggestions about this web site, please notify the [Web Manager](mailto:webmaster@marriagebuilders.com).  
© 1996-2000 Marriage Builders, Inc. Marriage Builders is a registered trademark of Marriage Builders, Inc.
